li like said welcome brothers and
sisters to another Wednesday question
and answer will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
whole world to keep brother tanel and
God spake all these words saying I am
the Lord thy God which have brought thee
out of the land of Egypt out of the
house of bondage thou shall have no
other gods before me thou not make to
thee any Graven image or any likeness of
anything that is in heaven above or that
is in the earth beneath or that is in
the water under the Earth thou shall not
bow down thyself to them nor serve them
for the Lord thy God am a jealous God
visit thing the iniquities of the
fathers upon the children unto the third
and fourth generation of them that hate
me and showing Mercy unto thousands of
them that love me and keep my
Commandments thou shall not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain for the
Lord will not hold young guilers that
take up his name in vain remember the
Sabbath day to keep it holy six days
should th LA and do all thy work but the
seventh day is the Sabbath of the Lord
thy God in it thou shall not do any work
thou nor thy son nor th daughter thy man
servant nor thaty maid servant nor thy C
nor th Strang that's within thy gates
for in six days the Lord may heaven and
earth the sea and all that in them M and
rested the seventh day wherefore the
Lord blessed the Sabbath day and
hollowed it honor thy father and thy
mother that thy days may be long upon
the land which the Lord thy God giveth
thee
thou shall not kill thou shall not
commit adultery thou shall not steal
thou shall not best fall witness against
thy neighbor thou sh not cover the
neighbor's house thou not cover that
neighbor's wife nor his man servant nor
his maid servant nor his Ox nor his ass
nor anything that is thy neighbors weere
Exodus 21-17 and may the Lord have a
blessing to the reading of his words in
Jesus name we pray amen
amen so here question and answer you can
ask us a question and we'll answer it
according to the King James Bible and if
we cannot find the answer we will seek
further counsel to bring you an answer
at a later time keep in mind that all
vague questions would not be answered
and all long scripture questions would
not be answer for time sake but we may
be able to point you in the direction of
a DVD or CD that you can purchase by
calling the office so please be as
direct as possible with your questions
so we can be as direct as possible with
our aners out of the King James Bible no
other Bibles will be acknowledged on
this program also keep in mind that this
is a live stream and you may begin to
send in your questions at this time even
questions that pertain to everlasting
life we just ask that you keep your
questions to a two scripture maximum but
let me introduce you to family that's on
the panel this evening brother Julius
good evening everybody brother Dre good
evening brother Jerome Grace and peace
Brother tanzel good evening everyone
sister Deborah good evening brother Shan
good evening and we have the guest
caller with us and I'm brother Cornell
sister Deborah what is our first
question of the evening yes there are
several uh questions that will be
answered first before getting into
tonight's Q&A so uh Sharon Seymour says
I would like confirmation of Jeremiah
49 vers 10-1
17 focusing on 10 and 13 after
confirming should I consider myself a
stranger because my grandmother was
mixed also what happens to the strangers
in
heaven all right brother Julius we're g
to let you hit that question right there
on this um we know no one's in heaven
but go ahead my brother uh good evening
everybody that's a a lot a lot uh got
about four questions in in in these one
question let's go brother tenzel to
Jeremiah
49 and then I want to start at verse 7
and Skip because this whole whole uh
chapter is about the Judgment upon Edom
or adum or the people that call
themselves uh Jewish people
today they are really
49 and 7 let's look at what the
subject matter is go ahead concerning
Edom thus said the Lord of hosts is
wisdom no more in teing is councel
perish from prudent is their wisdom
vanished
so skip down to verse 10 cuz he's
questioning verse 10 Look What the Lord
said go ahead but I have made Esau bear
I have uncovered his secret places he
shall not be able to hide himself and
his seeus Bo and his Brethren and his
neighbors and he is not so now the Lord
said I have made Esau B which mean that
I have exposed Esau I have exposed him
and we know who they are we know who
they are and the world calls them the
Jewish people but we know who they
really are
but what about Edom verse 11 what else
about it go ahead quickly leave thy
fatherless children I will preserve them
Al Li and let thy widows trust in me the
Lord said I'm not going to destroy them
all because this is a judgment upon Edom
you can read the thing what he going to
do in the book of Obadiah but skip down
to verse 13 and let's uh unscramble that
one go ahead for I have sworn by myself
sayeth the Lord that b r shall become a
desolation a reproach a waste and a
curse and all the cities thereof shall
be Perpetual Oasis so bosra is uh one of
the cities of edom's territory he said I
have swor by myself that b shall be a
desolation the Lord going to do this
when he return He said when the whole
world is at rest I'm going to punish
Edom for all their transgressions but he
said I'm going to leave a remnant of
them I will leave a remnant of
and ask for your question about
uh you being a mixed um it is the man
that carried the seed I know it is
so-called Jewish tradition that the
mother or the grandmother carried the
seed but it is the man that carried the
seed and all of the three sons of Noah
shim ham and japheth it is always the
man that carried the seed and what
happened to The Strangers In Heaven
Again nobody goes to heaven the book
says thy kingdom come thy will be done
on Earth so he going to bring it is
called the Kingdom of Heaven because
it's prepared there but he going to
bring it down to the Earth and let me
show you what the Lord is going to do to
all the strangers and all the people
that make the cut or that are righteous
in his eyes Isaiah 56
chapter Isaiah chapter 56 you have to
read the whole scripture the Lord is the
merciful god and his desire that no one
perish Isaiah
56 pick it up at verse two Isaiah 56-2
go ahead blessed is the man that doeth
this and the son of man that layth hold
on it that keepeth the Sabbath from
polluting it and keepeth his hand from
doing any evil what is the Lord going to
do that verse five go
ahead even unto then will I give in my
house within my walls of place and a
name better than of sons and of
daughters and I will give them an
everlasting name that shall not be cut
off continue
also the sons of the stranger that join
themselves to the Lord to serve him and
to love the name of the Lord to be his
servants everyone that keepeth the
Sabbath from pollutin it and taketh hold
of my Covenant one more verse brother
even then will I bring to my Holy
Mountain and make them joyful In My
House of Prayer their burnt offering and
their sacrifices shall be accepted upon
my Altar for my house shall be called a
house of prayer for all people
so somebody from All Nations got to be
in the Lord's House of Prayer and that
includes a remnant of Edom so keep the
Commandments and you can enter into the
kingdom of God and verse eight the Lord
told you he said I got others that them
to that I not of the household of Israel
them too I must bring in that's the best
that I can do with that
Cornell all right thank you for that
brother hope that answered that question
as we move on to our
next next one one Byron says in Matthew
12:12 it let us know that it is lawful
to do well on the Sabbath days does
helping someone stranded on the side of
the road changing a tire count is doing
well let's go to Matthew 12 we'll open
this up to the
panel Matthew
12 and pick it up that
uh verse 12 because they want to know
about helping someone stranded on the
side of the road change at Tire count as
doing well go right ahead
brother how much then is a man better
than a sheep so wherefore is it lawful
to do well on the Sabbath
days open to the panel yeah it's good to
to do well on the Sabbath day you know
absolutely that's right yep so you know
even when it comes to changing the tire
you got to be careful out there a lot of
people get hurt or killed even with
changing tires so you know sometimes
triaa is there to do their job but make
sure safety is uh your main
priority if you see the need to to want
to help out in that
situation yes sir all
right go right ahead where we going
to Matthews 12 and read 10
through3 and behold there was a man
which had his hand with him they asked
him saying is it lawful to heal on the
Sabbath days that they might accuse him
and he said unto them what man shall
there be among you that shall have one
Sheepman if it fall into a pit on the
Sabbath day will he not lay hold on it
and it out
go ahead how much then is a man better
than a sheep wherefore is it lawful to
do well on the Sabbath days then say he
to the to the man stretch forth thy hand
and he stretched it forth and it was
restored whole like as the
up now he could have waited till the
next day to do that but there was
something that needed to be done at that
very moment same thing with the ti do
his will to do that okay all right hope
that answered your question there we're
going to move on to our next one moving
on sister Israel says if I explain a
situation or reflect on my past whether
negative or positive not slandering
talking down or speaking ill towards
anyone that involves me is that tail
bearing
let's open that up to the
panel and they go
out
not well as long as it's not causing any
ill uh uh uh you know not is not causing
to you know any ill uh uh uh feeling
toward
nobody accusing it
like you said long as it like that then
it's not tail Bearer but a tail Bearer
don't mean because that you lying on
somebody sometime you can carry a tail
and it could be true but it could cause
a whole lot of damage and sometime it be
left better not said anything not being
said about it at all right people say
think because you use the word tailbar
it is something untrue sometime you can
tell the truth Bible speaks about
sometime uh uh uh love covers a lot of
sin if it won't do no good why talk
about
it it depends on what you're talking
about even if it's about yourself that's
all I have to say right be careful who
you shared
with all
right hope that answered your question
as we continue to move on to our next
continuing on
AHS are the sons of God in Genesis
chapter 6
angels are the sons of God in Genesis
Angels what you got for that brother Dre
no they are not let's go to Genesis
6 Genesis 6 and read verses one and
two and three go ahead brother and it
came to pass when men began to multiply
on the face of of the earth and
daughters were born unto them that the
sons of God saw the daughters of men
that they were Fair they took them wives
of all which they choose and the Lord
said my spirit shall not always drive
with man for that he is also flesh and
his days shall be 120 years notice it
said that these sons of God saw the
daughters of men and they took them
wives of all which they chose that mean
they married women of all which they
chose and the Lord said my spirit will
not always strive with man for that he
is also flesh man didn't say Angels it
said man right now let's go to Matthew
22nd chapter Matthew
22 and we gonna pick it up at
verse
28 there was a question asked
the the son had a didn't have a child he
died and all these other children died
so the the Pharisees wanting to tempt
Jesus said well whose wife is she gonna
be in the
resurrection look at this answer here
verse 28 go ahead therefore in the
resurrection whose wife shall she be of
the seven for they all had her uhhuh and
Jesus answered and said unto them ye do
not knowing the scriptures nor the power
of
God on the resurrection they neither
marry nor are given in marriage but are
as the angels of God in heaven they
don't in the resurrection you don't
marry nor are you given in marriage just
like the Angels do not marry nor are
they given in marriage let's go to one
more place Romans
8 Romans
8 and let's read verses 13 and
14 go ahead brother when you get
it but if you be for if you live after
the flesh you shall die but if you live
through the spirit do mortify the Deeds
of the body ye shall
live for as many as are led by the
spirit of God they are the sons of God
that's right as many as are led by the
now it said in Genesis 6 that the Lord's
Spirit won't always strive with man
because he is also flesh right and
that's what man was doing at that
time and they no longer were led by the
spirit but they were led by their
flesh so that's what that's talking
about it's not talking about
angels but angels can live longer than
120 years that is
right again was really in the first
scripture he wrote they are also flesh
angels are spirits right right okay two
different beings all together
exactly that is correct all right hope
that answered your question as we move
on to our next one moving on we can talk
right here as does the fourth
Commandment mean to draw mean no drawing
Angels or things in the sea like fish
can you
explain well you you can draw I mean you
can draw some angels and you can draw
fish in the sea and a lot of God's other
creation uh let's go to Exodus 20 I know
some people are very skillful when they
drawing
abilities Exodus 20
and let's pick it up brother let's pick
it up at that verse
um verse eight they said right said the
fourth
Commandment verse eight go
ahead
um Romans I'm sorry Exodus 20 and verse
eight Exodus 20 and8 we read it earlier
but we we'll give it a read
again okay
remember the Sabbath day to keep it holy
okay so they was asking about drawing
fish and and angels and things of that
nature sure you can do that just don't
do verse three and four read three and
four
brother thou shall have no other gods
before me thou shall not make unto thee
any Graven image or any likeness of
anything that is in heaven above or that
is in the earth beneath or that is in
the water under the Earth
yeah so once you get into that
worshiping or thinking that by your hand
you drew something that's worth bowing
down to don't do that but as far as just
drawing you're free to do that you can
draw angels fishing other things that
your heart desire just can't worship it
or bow down to it that's all I
get yeah plus if somebody can find it
right quick when they built the temple
they had painted on the wall palm tree
and a Cher Angel palm tree Cher of
angels even on the uh uh uh the uh veil
in the temple they had
Angel Cher Angels drawn on it somebody
can find that right quick all right went
in search mode for
that and so in this this uh this the the
Tabernacle of the congregation and the
temple was dictated by God he told him
what to
do that's uh Ezekiel
41 okay read
it that's Ezekiel 41 yeah pick it up all
right the
18 and it was made with cherubs and palm
trees so that the palm trees was between
the Cherub and the cherubs and every ch
had two
faces so that the faces of a man was
towards the palm trees on the one side
and the face of the Young Lion towards
the palm trees on the other side and it
was made through all the house round
about one more voice one more verse from
the
ground unto above the door were CH rooms
and palm trees made and on the wall of
the
temple so that so that's it you know you
had pictures there a chair up in palm
trees on the wall of the temple on the
uh uh uh uh you know the the ve of the
temple that separated the holy from the
most holy place it's not the picture
it's the Bowing down to them is what is
what
VI okay yep that is correct so draw your
heart out but don't bow down all right
that is let's move on to our next
question sister moving on Zion asked in
Proverbs 18 verse
22 if a woman is not married does that
mean she is not a good thing or not
favorite of the
Lord oh not Proverbs 18:22 brother
Julius what you got let's read that
tenzel
Proverbs and 22 who so findeth a wife
findeth a good thing and obtain favor
Lord that's all that's saying it does
not mean that if you are single that
you're not a good person or a good
woman it just said whoo found a wife
find a good thing and obtain favor of
the Lord
but if you are not married let's go to
First Corinthians the 7th chapter let's
look at how we should how uh we could
what the Lord say about if you are
unmarried First Corinthians the seventh
chapter brother
tenzel and please
read pick it up at verse uh
32 but I will have you without
carefulness he that is unmarried care
for the things that belong to the Lord
how he may please the Lord but he that
is married care for the things that are
of the world how he may please his wife
34 there is a difference also between a
wife and a virgin the unmar woman care
for the things of the Lord that she may
be holy both in body and in spirit but
she that is Mary care for the things of
the world how she may please her husband
so if you're not married sister hey then
let the Lord be your husband and do the
things that's pleasing to
him and if you are
married then the Lord is the head of the
husband and the wife that's all I
got right hope that answered your
question as we keep on moving yes uh
byan Israel ask in first Timothy 4
verse4 is your gift manifested with the
land on the hands of the
pretry and he also gave second Timothy 1
verse vers 6 so the first one is 1
Timothy 4
verse4 and the second one is second
Timothy 1 verse
6 all right Jerome share some
light let's go um read it brother
tanzel right uh neglect not the gift
that is in thee which was given thee by
Prophecy with the laying on the hands of
the presbyter
and the other one second
Timothy second Timothy 1
[Music]
and six one and six yeah y wherefore I
put thee in remembrance that thou stir
up the gift of God which is in thee by
the putting on of my hands yeah so yeah
you know that's one of the ways um it
could be manifested you know but that's
not the only way the gifts can be
manifested okay let's go to Mark
16 Mark 16 and pick it up at the 15 Read
to the
18 and he said unto them go ye into all
the world and preach to gospel to Every
Creature he that believeth and is
baptized shall be saved but he that
believeth not shall be
damned and these signs shall follow them
that believe in my name shall they cast
out Devils they shall speak with new
tongues they shall take up serpents and
if they drink any deadly thing it shall
not hurt them but they shall lay hands
on the sick and they shall
recover yeah skip down verse
20 and they went forth and preached
everywhere the Lord working with them
and confirming the word with signs
following amen yeah so is that's not the
only way just landay on the hand of PR
and tell the only way the gifts can be
distributed or administered it can be
administered by having faith in your God
keeping his Commandments and the Lord
working with you right yeah anybody else
can ask something if you
want you're right
brother what was talking about when
Jesus was taken up you say he left gift
Comm man and he named some of them
somebody can find that right
quick all right search mode for that and
he gave some Apostles
right
y um
Ephesians go ahead where Ephesians 4
and8 read it
wherefore he said when he Ephesians
4 that's right Ephesians 48 but it it
hit it at go down to
11 oh yeah yeah yeah you want me to
start at well you can you can hit it uh
just hit eight and then go down to
11 wherefore he said when he ascended up
on high he left captivity captives and
gave gifts unto men now he left
and he gave some Apostles and some
prophets and some evangelists and some
pastors and teachers for the perfecting
of the Saints for the work of the
ministry for the edifying of the body of
Christ all right all right hope that
answered your question there as we move
on to our next moving to the next one we
can talk right here as our stars that we
see in the night sky really Angels or
something
else all right that's caller can you
share some light are stars that we see
in the night sky are those angels or is
it something else well there something
else they certainly ain't
Angels now let's go in let's go into
Genesis the 1st chapter read verses 14
through 17
all right Genesis
1:14 y uhuh and God
said okay and God said let there be
lights in the firmament of of the heaven
to divide the day from the night let
them be for signs and for season and for
days and years and let them be for
lights in the firmament of the heaven to
give light upon the Earth and it was so
and God made two great lights two
greater lights to Rule the Day and the
Lesser light to rule the night and he
made the Stars also and God set them in
the firmament of the heaven to give
light upon the
Earth so that's what so the Not Angels
they are whatever uh material the Lord
used like the sun is one thing the Moon
is something and then the Stars also but
there was all to give light on the earth
they are not living creatures like the
angels are
that's
it all right hope that answered your
question next
question next question uh Malik Shakur
asks what is being blessed I hear a lot
of people saying they are blessed
because they have nice cars big houses
and other
things brother Dre what you say about
being blessed yeah I mean it's it's a
blessing if you got a house and it's
cold outside and you got a car to drive
and you ain't on the bus stop but the
blessing that the Lord is talking about
let's go to Luke the 11th chapter Luke
11 and read verses 27 and
28 Luke 11 2728 go ahead
brother
11 and it came to pass as spake these
things certain woman of the company
lifted up her voice and said unto him
blessed is the womb that bear thee and
the PS with thou H SED and he said yeah
rather blessed are they that hear the
word of God and keep it that's who's
blessed they that hear the word of God
and keep it let's go to revelation 22
and read verse
14 read it when you get there brother
bless they that do his Commandments that
they might have right to the tree of
life and may enter in through the gates
into the city that's right that's who's
blessed that's right word of God and do
it and keep his Commandments yes sir
when you read in in Matthew the fth
chapter it talks about a bunch of things
that we are blessed even when we going
through something if we enduring this
thing there's a blessing at the other
end of it so Matthew 5 on and 3 to2 on
your own read that it'll definitely help
yes sir bless are the poor bless are
they that mourn bless are the meek yes
sir yes sir that's true yes indeed
brother Dre those that endure to the end
also the same shall be blessed that's
right yes sir all right thank you for
that brother hope that answered your
question next one next one he also says
why when you try to live right and keep
the Commandments you live a lonely life
no friends or being close with family
because I refuse to do things not
pleasing to
God all right brother Julius sound like
a sword is in the mix go ahead bro that
is right uh that is right
congratulations brother you have just
been Sanctified or set
apart when you come when you come into
the knowledge of the truth you uh the
the the Lord has opened up your
understanding you're in the world but
you're not of the world let's look at
what the scriptures
say let's go to Matthew the 10th
chapter Matthew chapter 10
tzel because this is what people don't
understand they think that when you come
into the true knowledge of God that
everything is going to be smooth and
easy and everything going to be
wonderful uhuh let's look at what the
book says Matthew 10 beginning at verse
34 think not that I am come to send
peace on Earth I came not to send peace
but a sword and the sword is dropped
into your house how go ahead T I am come
to set a man at Vance against his father
and the daughter against her mother and
the daughter-in-law against her
mother-in-law uhhuh a man fold shall be
there of his own household a man's fold
shall be those of his own household when
you come to the truth mama not going to
like y'all of a sudden Daddy not going
to like you all of a sudden that is your
mother and your father you honor them
because they're your mother and your
father but spiritually
spiritually uh they they're they're your
foes because you're you're doing
something different you're in the book
you keeping the Commandments of God
you're keeping the dietary law so on and
so forth so but what you have to
understand is that you're never alone
you got a whole family h a church uh h
family when you uh who supposed to love
you and support you let me lead you with
this right here let's go to
Deuteronomy let me see if this is what I
want Deuteronomy because Deuteronomy
311 Deuteronomy
31 you're not alone
Deuteronomy 31 and Look What the Lord
commanded Us in the days of Moses even
to this day verse six go ahead quickly
be strong and of good courage fear not
nor be afraid of them for the Lord thy
God he it is that do goeth with thee he
will not fail thee nor forsake Thee the
Lord said I will not fear you and I will
not forsake you just stay with me one
more place my last place Psalm
27 Psalm
27 no you're not lonely matter of fact
you supposed to
Rejoice Paul said through much
tribulation we must enter into the
kingdom of God Psalm 27 my brother K and
give me verse
10 27 go ahead t for my father and my
mother forsake me then the Lord will
take me up but but until then this what
we have to continue to do verse
14 wait on the Lord wait on the Lord be
of good courage be strong he shall
strengthen thy heart wait I say on the
Lord so you stay with him you stay with
the Lord no matter what's going through
because you're going through a trial
you're going through a trial and you got
the the book said he that endureth until
the end the same shall be saved that's
all I got Corel yes sir indeed
brother Jesus say he come to bring a
sword you you go and when it's part of
the armor of God said the sword of the
spirit is the word of God okay that's
that SW he bring the word you got the
word they
don't read that Ephesians the 6
chapter yeah okay therefore you are
separated from them that's when you you
are thoroughly
Sanctified yep be thankful and let your
light shine that's right all right hope
that answered your question as we move
on to our next question next question
Miss Wade asked in Colossians 1 verse 13
what does this scripture mean has
translated us into the kingdom of his
dear son
please explain the word translate here
all right brother Jerome can you help
miss weit out on that
question let's go read it um Colossians
and13 actually can you pick it up at the
12 and read to the
okay go ahead Colossians 1 and 12 yeah
through
14 giving thanks unto the Father which
have made us meat to be partakers of his
inheritance of the Saints in light who
have delivered us from the power of
darkness and have translated us into the
kingdom of his dear son in whom we have
Redemption through his blood even the
Forgiveness of
sins yeah so let's simply put it you
know the Lord has delivered us from
false Doctrine he done delivered us from
the Ws of the devil if we believe in him
and trust in him keep his Commandments
he has delivered us all right from the
power of Darkness you know and if we
continue there in he said you got
everlasting life and he said he going to
raise you up at the last day so he he
done translate you in the Kingdom but
you got to you got to wait until the
appointed time which is the last day
when he change your vow body and fashion
like unto his glorious body okay so
um I was going to go to uh 1 Corinthians
the 4th
chapter I'm sorry second Corinthians
second Corinthians the 4th chapter read
verse skip six and Skip to verse
14 for God who commanded the light to
shine out of Darkness have shine in our
hearts to give the light of the
knowledge of the glory of God in the
face of Jesus Christ and through him
through his blood through his word we
can be delivered go ahead and Skip to
verse 14 knowing that he which raised up
the Lord Jesus shall raise us up also by
Jesus and shall present us with
you St John chapter 6 and verse 40 and
that'll be it
right St John
6 and this is the will of him that sent
me that everyone which seeth the son and
Believe on him may have everlasting life
and I will raise him up at the last day
yeah so translated is he just told you
you got everlasting life but I ain't GNA
raise you up until the last day and
that's the coming that's the coming of
the Lord
that's plus again to translated that
mean that he are giving you a new way of
thinking you become a new person it's
written in there right you know you put
off the old man and put on the new man
right one that's walking in newness of
Life other words you're walking in the
word of God that's right all that mean
is you have
changed you're well
thank yep indeed what a blessing all
right hope that answered your question
as we move on to our next one next One
rodri D Hanes says please explain to
listeners how important it is to keep
the high days according to their seasons
and
times all right guess
caller well you do it because God said
it yep go to Leviticus 23 and read verse
4 these are the feasts of the Lord even
holy convocation which he shall Proclaim
in their
season now he said you should the Lord
said You shall Proclaim them in their
season right now if you want to the rest
of it how what each up mean then that is
too much to answer on Q&A what you do is
you show up on each one of these feasts
and and listen and each one of them will
speak for itself but the main reason
it's important for you to do it like
because the Lord said keep them in their
Seas that's all I have to say right we
we also got a lesson called the Feast of
the Lord if you want to get an early
jump all
right next question that might be coming
up that
lesson it's
possible all right sister
DEA yes next question Kenisha Mia says
can you explain Luke
16: 22- 26 are they already in hell what
is Abraham's
bosom only one of them was in Hell which
is the Lake of Fire which is a condition
that I'm sure he'll spend eternity
regretting that he ended up there but
let's go to Luke
16 Luke
16 and let's pick it up when you get
there brother at that verse they want to
pick it up at verse
22 let's pick it up
at yeah let's pick it up verse 19 and
read go ahead
there was a certain rich man which was
clothed in purple and fine linen Fair
sumptuously every day uhuh was a certain
beggar named Lazarus which was laid at
his gate full of Swords yeah so keep in
mind here rich man doing real good
living a good life and Lazarus is on the
suffering end at this time but they go
end up changing places basically go
ahead bro and Desiring to be fed with
the crumbs which fell from the rich man
table more of the dogs came and lifted
up his
swords and it came to pass that the
beggar died and was carried by the
Angels into Abraham's bosom the rich man
also died and was buried all
right and in hell he lifted up his eyes
being in torment and see of Abraham a
far off and laders in his
bosom it says and in hell he lift up his
eyes being in torment this is the Lake
of Fire here that the rich man was in so
he didn't make the cut but Lazarus he
had also died but he is a part of
everlasting life here and so is Abraham
go ahead and he cried and said Father
Abraham have mercy on me and send
Lazarus that he may dip the tip of his
finger in water and cool my tongue for I
am tormented in this flame
yeah but Abraham said Son remember that
thou in thy lifetime receiveth thy good
things likewise Lazarus evil things but
now he is comforted and thou are
tormented yeah so the rich man dressed
nice ate good every day and Lazarus just
looking for some of the crumbs that fell
from the rich man's table but he
wouldn't he wouldn't do it by him go
ahead and beside all this between us and
you there is a great golf fixed so that
they which would pass from hence to you
cannot hether can they pass to us that
will come from this so this is speaking
about only the rich man being in hell
right here and in this state of
condition which was the Lake of Fire
Abraham and Lazarus hey they had
everlasting life and when it talks about
the word bosom it's a few things that
kind of Define bosom because you wanted
to know what did it mean that that
Lazarus was in Abraham's bosom well
bosom is chest or or breast or even to
embrace somebody and sometimes when you
got your arm around somebody and got
them held tight that can be considered
to be the bosom too so you have
different variables there but just
saying they were standing side by side
in an Embrace as it was being broke down
on one living good and now suffering and
one suffering and not living good good
so Lazarus ended up in a good place even
though he suffered when he was in the
flesh that is also symbolic of being
Abraham budm also symbolic of being on
the right side of the kingdom of
God all right I want to add something to
this first thing is Jesus gave a parable
there but that could not take place
until after the white Throne judgment
yes sir that's right talk about because
let me show you uh uh let's go to
Revelation 19th Chapter we going to show
you who
was first people that hit the Lake of
Fire Revelation 19 start at verse
19 and I saw the Beast and the Kings on
on the earth their armies gathered
together to make war against him that
sat on the horse and against his Army
and the Beast was taken and with him the
false prophet that wroth Miracles before
him with which he deceived them that
have received the mark of the beast and
them that worship His Image these both
were cast alive into a lake of fire
burning with
Brimstone now that's when Jesus come
these are the first two people going to
hit the Lake of Fire and nobody else
going to hit the lake of fire until
after the white Throne judgment go to
Revelation 20th chapter and start at
verse
11 and I saw a great white throne and
him that sat on it from who
face let's back up because after this uh
uh uh they was loose after after being
and and uh uh being locked up for uh uh
for a thousand years let's see what he
did when he was loose start at verse 9
this what Satan did he went up on the
breath of the earth start at verse n Go
ahead and they went up on the breath of
the earth and compassed the camp of the
Saints about
and the belov city and fire came down
from God out of heaven and devoured them
and the devil that deceiveth them were
cast into the lake of fire and brimstone
where the Beast and the false prophet
are and shall be Tor day and
night the Beast and the false prophet
and the rich
man yeah no is that what it said nope it
said what the false the Beast and the
false prophet are
so now the rich man did not get
healed go to lopy until after the white
Throne judgment and as far as Lazarus is
concerned that mean that he was in the
good part of the kingdom and the rich
man was in the bad part of the Kingdom
which is the Lake of Fire but down of
that none of that cannot take place
until after the white Throne judg
because the rich man will not be in the
first resurrection he going be in his
Jud and if he come up
and then he will get cut off get around
and and the read the next one they were
J right read the next
one and I saw the dead
small great stand before God and the
books were open and another book was
open which is The Book of Life and the
dead
were now let's see what happened in the
Book of Life was there and the did was
judg out of the books according to their
work skip down to verse 15 let's see who
going to go into into the Lake of Fire
and whosoever was not found written in
the Book of Life was cast into the Lake
of
Fire so what so Jesus gave that Parable
that was something that ain't going to
happen until after the white Throne
judgment man will not go to the white
Throne judgment until I mean to go to
the lopy until after the white Throne
judgment so none of that's taking place
even today I just want to throw that in
there
all right okay hope that answered your
question nobody can afford that Lake of
Fire all right next question sister with
the time check yes the time is
8:20 and uh in Matthew 19 ver 5 and 6 zi
says does this scripture mean to become
one spiritually
and not physically meaning on one Accord
with the Bible but he doesn't have to
share house car or anything
material all right Tel one we go to at
Matthew
19 and pick it up at that five read five
and six and the guest caller take it
from
there and said for this cause shall a
man leave father and mother and shall
cleave to his wife and they twain shall
be one flesh butfor they are no more
Twain but one flesh what therefore God
have joined together let no man put a
th that mean that both of them are
living in the same
house both of them thinking on the same
order because they agree to get married
because that is a
covenant let's go into Genesis the 2
chapter and we're going to read Verse 18
then we going to skip down 21 and
22 after that verse 24 read it when you
get there and the Lord God said is not
it is not good that man shall be alone
but I will make him and help me for him
now pay attention to this thing it is
not good that man shall be alone right
right yep and he shouldn't be by himself
right
mhm he help
me now skip
down to verse
21 and read 21 and
22 and the Lord God calls a deep sleep
to fall upon Adam he slept and he took
one of his ribs and closed up the flesh
instead thereof and the rear which the
Lord God had taken from man made he a
woman and brought her her unto the
man so now he took his rib and made a
woman and brought her to the man God
could have went in the ground and dug
something else out of it and made a
woman out of it but he didn't want to do
that he took the woman out of the man
because the woman is a part of man
therefore when he made her woman he
brought her to man now skip down in
verse 24 see what it says therefore
shall a man leave his father and his
mother
and shall cleave unto his wife and they
shall be one
flesh that mean you supposed to leave
them not only
spiritually other words God you handle
your own business don't let your family
handle it and physically you supposed to
go and like it said you going to leave
your father and your mother and you go
and you live with your spouse Point
Blank otherwise you still alone if
you're not and God said man should not
be alone that's all I have to say all
right hope that answered your question
there sister Deborah are we going into
new
territory yes and so we are now into
tonight's Q&A for Wednesday October the
30th
2024 um Israel for life as can you
explain
if God's law is described as perfect and
lifegiving in places like Psalms 19
verse 7 what does it mean in Ezekiel 20
verse
25 where God says he gave
statutes excuse me he gave SC
stat he gave stat
that were not good and rules by which
they could not have life so let me do
that
again Israel for Life ask can you
explain if God's law is described as
perfect and lifegiving in places like
Psalms 19 verse
7 what does it mean in Ezekiel 20 verse
25 where God says he gave statutes that
were not good and rules by which they
could not have
life all right brother Dre what you say
two different things and you gonna see
the reasons why first let's go to Psalms
19 and we going to read verse 7 Psalms
and7 go ahead when you get it t
the law of the Lord is perfect
converting the soul the testimony of the
Lord is sure making wise the simple so
this is what the law does the law of the
Lord is perfect that's what it says read
verse
11 moreover by them is thy servant Warn
and in keeping of them there is great
reward there's great reward in keeping
the Commandments of God which is life
right great reward if you keep them now
let's go to Ezekiel the 20th chapter and
read what happened there because this is
not that he gave them the law and and
they being punished here this is not
what this talking about so Ezekiel 20
let's start at verse 24 instead of 25 go
ahead brother because they had not
executed my judgment but had despised my
statues and had polluted my sabbaths and
their eyes were after their father's
Idols this is what happened so because
they did this this is what happened read
to verse
25 wherefore I gave them also statues
that were not good in judgment whereby
they should not
live and I polluted them in their own
gifts and that they caus to pass through
the fire all that open the womb and I
might make them desolate to the end that
they might know that I am the Lord the
Lord polluted them in their own gifts he
gave them over to their own lust let's
read one more example of that let's go
to Romans the first
chapter we gonna read Verse 18 when you
get it tanel go
ahead they should read that whole
chapter yes
sir what was that Romans Romans 1 verse
18 for the wrath of God is revealed from
Heaven against all ungodliness and
unrighteousness of men who hold the
truth and unrighteousness SK down to 21
because that when they knew God they
glorify him not as God neither were
thankful but became vain in their
imaginations and their foolish heart was
darkened Ohad professing themselves to
be wise they became fools and because
they did that this is what happened
verse 24 go ahead wherefore God also
gave them up to uncleanness through the
lust of their own Hearts to dishonor
their own bodies between
themselves so God gave them up to what
it is that they lust was
after yeah God gave them Commandments
for them to keep and because they didn't
keep them all this he gave them over to
their own lust right that's all that
happened
read a little bit more just a little
more go ahead go ahead guest
call finish what you reading go ahead I
just want
to let him keep
reading who change the truth of God into
a lie and worship and serve the creature
more than the Creator who is blessed
forever amen
26 for this cause God G them up into
vile affection
for even that women did change the
natural use that which is against nature
and likewise men working that which is
unnatural men with men now gave them
over to they
lust because they did not want to keep
what God said in order for us to keep
guess
call
M okay 2 Thessalonians the 2 chapter
read verse 11 and
12 oh they don't want to deal with the
truth they going to follow uh preachers
that do uh that lie what's God going to
do with them verse 11 and for this cause
God shall send them strong delusion that
they should believe a lie that they all
might be damned who believe not the
truth but have pleasure in
unrighteousness
that's
it right
wow like d said didn't want the truth so
God going to give them a strong illusion
that they might be downam yeah yeah and
what can you say Dre because like you
read that 21 because that when they knew
God they glorified him not as God nether
were thankful that's
right he gave them over to rep probate
M all right let us move on sister
Deborah to our next question yes Moving
On Patricia Henderson asked
will once we become
Immortals will our loved ones that's
been raised from the dead will we know
one
another um
yeah I mean why wouldn't
you because whatever you look like now
and whatever you got going on that is
yours to keep because um but let's go
into um where we going here let's go
into that
uh is that verse Dre me you talked about
that mat was it Matthew 17 I think so
yeah write it
down but yeah can you can you imagine
Adam and Eve seeing each other and
saying who are you that's Matthew
17 Matthew
17 all right we got Abraham and Sarah
that had Isaac they know who they son
was and Isaac turned around had
twins Jacob and Esau and then Jacob had
12 sons so read it let's go and read
that m Matthew 17
verse1 and after six and after six days
Jesus taketh Peter James and John his
brother and bringeth them up into a high
mountain
apart and was transfigure before them
and his face did shine as the sun and
his rment was white as the
light and behold there appeared unto
them Moses and Elias talking with
them behold Moses and he lies even
though they have died was there talking
with them and they had the same
appearance did you want to add something
to that Dre no that's it no that's it
well one other thing Parable that Jesus
gave about Abraham Lazarus and the rich
man didn't they all know one another
yeah that was after the resurrections
both up sure did y they knew one another
all right hope that answered your
question there as we keep on moving
keeping and moving Valencia says can you
tell me who are the
samarians hey Julius who are them
Samaritans you have the original
Samaritans who were
Israelites who were Israelites and they
occupi the northern capital of Israel
whose capital was Samaria judah's
Capital was Jerusalem so after um in 722
BC when uh the king of Assyria came and
well let's go read it let's go to Second
Kings the 17th chapter because the
Samaritan woman that Jesus talked to was
a descendant she was of hemic lineage
she was of the lineage of Canaan hites
Second Kings
penzel and pick it up at verse
17 Second Kings 17 and we gonna start
reading at verse 22 2 Kings 17 and
22 this is what happened
and pick it up at 22 go ahead brother
for the children of Israel walk in all
the sins of jobor which he had de and
they departed not from them so what
happened until the Lord removed Israel
out of his sight as he had said by all
his servants the prophet so was Israel
carried away out of their own land to
ayria unto this day so now Israel dwelt
after Solomon's death in Northern Israel
and they Samaria was their Capital
continue and the king of Assyria brought
men from Babylon unto Kar and from Ai
and from ha HTH and from Sean and placed
them in the city of Samaria and said the
children of Israel and they possessed
Samaria and dwelt in the cities thereof
so what
happened and so it was at the beginning
of their dwelling there they they that
they feared not the Lord therefore the
Lord sent Lions among them and slew some
of them so man the king uh want to know
what can we do these Lions is killing
our people these are hamites notice he
brought people in from Babylon but so
now what did the king of Assyria do and
this is how that woman got her knowledge
and when Jesus talked to the woman at at
the well verse
27 then the king of assy's commanded
saying heavy did the one of the priests
whom ye brought from from thence and let
them go and dwell there and let them
teach them the manner of the god of the
land so one of the priests that got
carried out of the land was brought back
so he could teach the strangers which
were which was the hamites uh about the
uh the god of Israel
so now but it said at at the end of 24
at the end in the middle of 24 and the
king of Assyria brought men from Babylon
and from CA and from abah and from Heath
notice how I spell Heath one more place
Genesis is the 10th chapter remember h a
m a t h Genesis chapter 10 let's see who
these are cuz these are black Nations
that were replaced that are that are
that repl another black nation which was
the original Israelite or the original
Samaritans Genesis
10 and pick it up at verse 15 Genesis 10
and 15 go ahead
T and Canan beg got sidon his first
verse six first verse six I'm sorry
verse six
first and the sons of ham Kush M and
foot and Canaan so now ham is is your
African nations Kush is your modern day
Ethiopians misraim is a slang Egypt is
the slang slang name from misraim put is
Libya and Canaan was the uh was where uh
the land was Israel were called before
Israel occupied it now skip down to
verse 15 and go
ahead and Canaan begot sidon his
firstborn in he and the jebusites and
the amorites and the gites and the hi es
and the arites and the
shites and the AR arites and the zores
and the hamites and that hamite there's
your hamite right there go ahead and
afterwards were the families of the
canites spread abroad so the original
Samaritans were Israelites and the king
of Assyria took them out in 722 BC and
replaced them with African nation black
uh uh hamic Nations and Israel was
scattered
so the people that you call Samaritans
and and your ask your question these
Samaritans were hamites the woman at the
well was a hamite that met Jesus that's
the best I can do with
that all right thank you for that
brother hope that answered that question
next
question uh yes and before we uh go to
the next question uh I just want to
State please uh Brothers in the
chat uh Brothers on um please do not
respond to the chat by answering the
questions that are in the chat please do
not do that leave that
alone so the next question is from Zion
Zion says I hear some Israelites say the
name you're supposed to to be baptized
in is
yua since Jesus is not his Hebrew name
true yes call them what you
say but the brother said that don't know
how they don't know
prophecy because God uh uh uh everything
everything that we study everything we
know about God everything even find out
of that we are Israelite we learn it out
of a document a Bible that's written in
English and everything that come in this
language is
valent and the Lord made that clear what
he was going to do let's go to Isaiah
28th chapter and we going to read from
verse 9 to 12 Isaiah 289
to2 Whom Shall he teach knowledge and
Whom Shall he make to understand
Doctrine them that are wean from the
milk and drawn from the
breast thing right here right quick he
said Whom Shall we teach knowledge isn't
that correct right y so now those are B
from milk and draam from the dress now
let's see how he going to teach him go
ahead and read for precept must be upon
upon precept precept upon preet ly upon
line lying upon line here a little and
there a little uhhuh but with a
stammering lip and another tongue will
he speak to this
people finish it to whom he said this is
the rest wherewith ye may cause the
weary to rest and this is the refreshing
yet they were not
here but the word of the Lord was now
when he said with men of other tongue
when he speaking his people that mean
other languages isn't that correct
right yeah so now that was written in
Hebrew so when the Lord and and never
speaking from the point of Hebrew so if
he said he going to with men of other
tongu will he speak to his people he's
the one going to give knowledge that
mean with men of other languages ain't
that correct
right now let's go into uh uh let's go
into 1 Corinthians the 14th chapter read
verse 20 and
21 1 Corinthians 14th
chapter verse
20 and
21 Brethren be not children in
understanding how B in Malice be ye
children but in understanding be
men uhuh in the law it is written with
men of other tongues and other lips will
I speak unto this people and yet for all
that
will they not hear me sayeth the Lord he
Isaiah
didn't
Isaiah I'm a man of another tongue I
speak English I don't speak
Hebrew do now that's why we baptized in
the name that was given to us in English
which is Jesus then the Lord himself Co
signed the name his name let's go into
Malachi 1 And1
1 read it when you get
there or from the rising of the sun even
until the going down of the saint my
name shall be great among the
Gentiles and in every place my name he
said this mean this is the Lord talking
ain't it that's right who
are European caucasians
the name that we call them white folks
white folks so what is the greatest name
among the white folks
Jesus now keep reading and in every
place incense shall be offered unto my
name and a pure offering for my name
shall be great among the Heathen sayeth
the Lord of
hosts the heathen mean the Nations right
that's right how many nations you know
that's running around talking about yua
huh east west north to south the
greatest name among the Nations and the
greatest name among the Gentiles is
Jesus that's why Paul said baptize the
people in the name of Jesus Peter
baptized the people in the name of Jesus
but the whole thing is when uh uh uh uh
that's what's written in our language
but Paul and Peter don't spoke Hebrew
ain't that
correct I mean so so man maybe they call
him
josua but then Peter them got beat and
Deni and told them not to even use that
name so we one the name that Israel that
these Israelite hate is the
Lord but the Lord cosigned himself he
said his name would be great among the
Gentiles and among the Nations
and he said he would speak Us in another
language we speak English
yeah that's all I got to say all right
right there go ahead that's why we
baptized in the name of Jesus that's it
yeah name of Jesus all right sister
Deborah we going to keep it moving time
is flying as we having fun
yes uh orando uh Davy asked to shed
light on First Corinthians 15 verse 29
can we be baptized for a dead loved
one all right let's go to 1 Corinthians
15 and 29 when you get there read it
brother tanzel they want to know can
they be baptized for a dead loved
one go ahead
brother else what shall they do which
are baptized for the dead if the dead
rise not at all why are they then
baptized for the dead gu call them first
thing years that didn't say nothing
about your dead loved on did it
nope so let's show what it really
mean let's go into Romans the 6th
chapter read verses 1-5
what shall we say then shall we continue
in sin that Grace May abound God forbid
how shall we that are dead to sin live
any longer
therein but know ye not that so many of
us as we're baptized into Jesus Christ
we're baptized unto his
death therefore we are buried with him
by baptism unto his death that like as
Christ was raised up from the dead by
the glory of the father even so we also
shall walk in newness of
Life what he saying to you just like
Jesus went in that water you know just
like Jesus was killed and he went in
that ground and he rose up alive we
shall go in that water that the old man
died in it and a new man come up out of
it go
ahead but if we have been planted
together in the likeness of his death we
shall be also in the likeness of his
resurrection and that's what we're
looking for there verse five right yes
sir go to First Corinthians 15th
chapter read verses 16-
18 well the dead rise not then is not
Christ raised and if Christ be not
raised your faith is vain yet ye are yet
in your
sins so now if the dead don't rise then
our faith is vain if Jesus didn't rise
our faith is vain did you finish that
the
18 we at 18 right now read it then they
also which I fallen asleep in Christ I
perish so
now baptism let you know that uh uh uh
uh you die with
Jesus and you raised with Jesus but if
there ain't no B if no Resurrection then
uh you baptized for nothing you have
perished but there is now but we going
to read one other
thing we're going to read the
uh First Peter 1 and three
read it when you get
there
Peter 1 Peter 1 and
3 blessed be the God and father of our
Lord Jesus Christ which according to His
abundant Mercy have begotten us again
unto a lively Hope by the resurrection
of Jesus Christ from the dead
so now that's what I we hoping is that
once we die we going to be raised from
the
grave just like and so the baptism that
baptism is baptizing under that it's
saying that just like you going in this
ground this water just like God Jesus
went into the ground just like Jesus
rose up just like you rise up Jesus rose
up as an immortal that represents you
coming up out this water and you are a
new person
person ver you're a new person because
you think different and your sins have
been washed so you baptized uh uh un not
unto a dead loved one you're
baptized to let you know that once you
die you going to rise again just like
Jesus went in the ground and came up you
going in the water and you came back up
that's all I have to say all right hope
that answers your question next question
next question Elizabeth Cockrell uh asks
if a person Pricks their finger that it
bleeds and their first instinct is to
put their finger in their mouth would it
be considered eating
blood open to the
pth
no go to Leviticus the chapter read
verse
26 yeah 7 I think it's 26 yeah Leviticus
7 and
26 moreover ye shall eat no man of blood
whether it be of a foul or of beast in
any of your
dwelling all I'm saying is if you going
cook a clean animal or a bird or
whatever it is you're not supposed to
eat the blood you flow the blood out and
you eat the meat in other words you a
supposed to eat no ra
steaks and you're not supposed to do
like the Italian do they have what they
call a duck blood soup but if you cut
your finger and you put it in your mouth
that don't mean you eating your
blood it's already in you about the
blood in the
animals all right hope that aned your
question we're in speed round next
question sister yes Dana Thomas ask if
each tribe will enter a gate with the
name of their tribe what gate do the
people who are spiritual Israel enter
Jerome uh the Believers are among the
other nations spiritual Israel if they
be pleased to sojourn among any tribe
whatever tribe they
among okay that's who G they going to
through all right let me show you let's
go to uh let's go to 48 Ezekiel 48 and
31 and then we're gonna go to the 47th
chapter after
that right Ezekiel 48 and just read
31 and the gates of the city shall be
after the names of the tribes of Israel
three gates northward one gate of Reuben
one gate of Judah and one gate gate of
Levi yeah so on so forth on down um to
the 35th verse but now I want you to go
to the uh 47th chapter pick it up at
21 so shall ye divide this land unto you
according to the tribes of
Israel it shall come to pass that you
shall divide it by life for inheritance
unto you and to the stranger that sour
among you which shall be got children
among you and they shall be unto you as
born in the country among the children
of Israel they shall have inheritance
with you among the tribes of
Israel and it shall come to pass that in
what tribe The Strangers sourn there
shall ye give him his inheritance sayeth
the Lord God yeah so it shall come to
pass that in what tribe The Stranger
sojourneth there ye shall give him his
inheritance and if you go through the
great Ruben and be PL to s be pleased to
Sur journ there that's gate he going to
walk through you know not saying he
ain't going to walk through other Gates
you
know but in answering to your question I
was just giving you the verse that's all
I
got okay thank you brother next question
next question sister jayen asked is
there a scripture that warns people
about what will happen to them if they
continue to listen to false preachers in
Psalms
perhaps yes
carer okay first let's start it with the
false
preacher Romans the first chapter read
Verse 18 and
19 what's the
script Romans chapter 1 18 and
19 for the wrath of God is revealed from
from Heaven against all ungodliness and
unrighteousness of men who hold the
truth in
unrighteousness because they which may
be known of God has manifested in them
for God have showed it unto
them now skip down to verse 28 read
it and even as they did not like to
retain God and their knowledge God gave
them over to a rep probate mind to do
those things which are not convenient
now not only them but let's see what
happened with those that believe in them
or co-sign thir verse
32 who knowing the Judgment of God that
they which commit such things are worthy
of death not only do the same but have
pleasure in them that do them so now the
people that do all these things and
false prophet teach false stuff and do
evil stuff and you listening to them God
going to destroy them and he all going
to destroy you because you Delight in
them if you following the false prophet
one of place let's go the chief of the
false prophets the man of sin 2
Thessalonians the 2
chapter once you get there read 1
through
four then we're going to skip
down now
we now we bece you Brethren by the
coming of our Lord Jesus Christ and by
our gathering together unto him that ye
be not soon shaken in mind or be
troubled neither by Spirit nor by word
nor by letters as from us as that the
day of Christ is at hand let no man
deceive you by any means for that day
should not come except there except
there come of Falling Away first and
that man of sin be revealed the son of
predition
who oppose and exalt himself above all
that is called God or that is worshiped
so that he as so that he as God sitting
in the temple of God showing himself
that he is
God now skip down to verse
n even him whose coming is after the
working of Satan all power and signs and
lying wonders and with all
deceivableness of unrighteousness in
them that perish because they receive
not the love of the truth that they
might be
saved and for this cause God shall send
them strong delusion that they should
believe a lie and they all might be
damned who believe not the truth but
have pleasure in
unrighteousness so if you keep listening
to them false
preachers and you know they lying you
and you don't investigate them then God
going to turn you get send you a strong
delion
so you will believe a lie that you might
be damn because when somebody come and
show you some truth you reject you and
don't try to investigate then that mean
you love this false Doctrine so the Lord
going to destroy you give you going to
give you a strong delusion that you
might be damned and if you are damned
you going to end up in the Lake of Fire
that's all I have to say yeah yeah
looking for the truth we'd be glad to
share it with you next question question
sister yes D asked are all Israelite
Believers or not going to the Wilderness
to be
taught yes call on all Israelite
Believers are not going to the
Wilderness to be
taught yes every Israelite on the planet
go to Isaiah 11th chapter read verse
10-2 Isaiah 11 10-2
Isaiah 11:10 through2 and at that day
there shall be a root of Jesse which
shall stand for inside of the people to
it shall the Gentiles seat and his rest
shall be glorious and it shall come to
pass in that day that the Lord shall set
his hand against the second time to
recover the remnant of his people which
shall be left from Assyria and from
Egypt and from pthos and from Kush and
from El
and from HTH and from the islands of the
sea do that mean he going to recover
everybody isn't that
correct
y uh read a little more what verse was
that that was in
11 read 12 and he shall set up an inside
for the Nations and shall assemble the
outcast of Israel and gather together
the disperse of Judah from the four
corners of the Earth
that mean everybody isn't that correct
that's right let's go to Ezekiel 20th
chapter read vers
33-36 Ezekiel 20:
33-36 as I live said the Lord God surely
with a mighty hand and with a stretched
out arm and with Fury poured out will I
rule over you and I will bring you out
of the people and will gather you out of
the countries wherein you are scattered
with a mighty hand and with the
stretched out on and with Fury poured
out and I will bring you into the
Wilderness of the people and there will
I plead with you face to face like as I
pleaded with your fathers in the
wilderness of the land of Egypt so will
I plead with you sayeth the Lord now
will cause you to pass under the rod and
I will bring you into the bond of the
Covenant and I will Purge out from among
you the rebels and them that transgress
against me I will bring them forth out
of the country where they sourn and they
shall not enter into the land of Israel
and ye shall know that I am the Lord am
the
Lord so now that's letting you know that
no matter where you are if you're
Israelite God's going to find you if
you're under a rock you're going to turn
it over and then some Gentile or
somebody going to pull you out and say
come we taking you back to Israel you
God and and they going to take you and
you going to go through that wilderness
just like every Israelite in Egypt came
out there was not one Israelite left in
Egypt when the Lord brought him out so
whether you believe or know that you're
Israelite or not it don't make no
difference God know who you
are everybody's going
through y all right thank you for that I
hope that answered your question sister
Deborah let's get this next
one all right uh the next one is
uh J will of God ask what is the
difference between a sin in an
Abomination Dre what you
say yeah all Abominations are
sin meaning an Abomination means that
God detests and regards an Abomination
with
disgust so Leviticus 11 speaks of the
dietary law in verse 12 it say whatever
got fins and scales shall be an
Abomination onto you and we should be
disgusted by
that uh Leviticus
1822 talks about men being with men it
being an Abomination women with women
let's go to uh Deuteronomy 7 Deuteronomy
7 and we going to read verses 2 5 and 26
go ahead when you get
it the brav image of their God shall ye
burn with fire thou shall not desire
this the silver or gold that is on them
nor take it unto thee lest thou be
snared therein for it is an Abomination
to the Lord thy God neither shallal thou
bring an Abomination to the house do
thou be a cursed thing like it but thou
shall utter distest it that thou shall
utterly uphor it for it is a cursed
thing we should uphor abominable things
and detest them now let's go to uh
proverb 6 read verses
16-19 Proverbs 6:1
16-19 go ahead
brother
okay these six things do the Lord
hat yeah seven are Abomination unto him
proud look a lying tongue and hands that
yet innocent blood a heart that devid
Wicked imagination feet that be Swift
and running to Mischief a false witness
that speak of lies and he that sth
Discord among Brethren so these things
are abominable to the Lord and He
detests
them this is what an Abomination is
about I hope that that helps and first
John 3:4 sin is the transgression of the
law the breaking of God's law yes
sir all right hope that answered your
question and sister Deborah this last
question here read
de okay uh the last question is from uh
dot
Martin and uh she says can you explain
Jesus answer to John and Luke 9 verse4
about casting out demons was John saying
only the 12 could cast out demons
because the verse didn't say this person
was an
unbeliever all right so do Martin we'd
like to inform you that that Luke 9 and4
has nothing in common with the question
that you asked so we asking that you
please resubmit your question so that we
can give you an answer to your questions
all right looks like we have ran out of
time right Deborah yeah yes the time is
9:05 oh yeah all right well we like to
thank everybody who tuned in with us
this evening want to thank you and if
you submitted a question and we didn't
have an opportunity to get to it don't
resubmit it we'll take your question and
we'll add it to the rotation and we'll
answer it next week so thank you all
again and until we all come together
again please be safe out there be
blessed and may the Lord have mercy on
us all brother tzel as you close us out
Our Father which are in heaven Hallowed
be thy name thy kingdom come thy will be
done in earth as it is in heaven give us
this day our daily bread and forgive us
of our debts as we forgive our debt to
us and lead us not into temptation but
Deliver Us from Evil for thine is the
kingdom and the power and the glory
forever in Jesus name we pray amen amen
amen